{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "55072c57eb1a8b41906ae35d" }, "question" : "Identify the sixth largest state.", "answer" : "Arizona", "author" : { "$oid" : "55072c56eb1a8b41906ae35c" }, "category" : "Geographical", "ratings" : [], "difficulty" : 2, "__v" : 0 }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "55072c57eb1a8b41906ae35e" }, "question" : "This state has the highest temperature on record of 134Â° F.", "answer" : "California", "author" : { "$oid" : "55072c56eb1a8b41906ae35c" }, "category" : "Geographical", "ratings" : [], "difficulty" : 1, "__v" : 0 }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "55072c57eb1a8b41906ae35f" }, "question" : "This state has the smallest population.", "answer" : "Wyoming", "author" : { "$oid" : "55072c56eb1a8b41906ae35c" }, "category" : "Geographical", "ratings" : [], "difficulty" : 3, "__v" : 0 }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "55072c57eb1a8b41906ae360" }, "question" : "The only state to consist of two peninsulas.", "answer" : "Michigan", "author" : { "$oid" : "55072c56eb1a8b41906ae35c" }, "category" : "Geographical", "ratings" : [], "difficulty" : 3, "__v" : 0 }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "55072c57eb1a8b41906ae361" }, "question" : "The only state that can be spelled using just one row of a QWERTY keyboard.", "answer" : "Alaska", "author" : { "$oid" : "55072c56eb1a8b41906ae35c" }, "category" : "Random", "ratings" : [], "difficulty" : 3, "__v" : 0 }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "55072c57eb1a8b41906ae362" }, "question" : "The only state where all its counties are classified as metropolitan areas", "answer" : "New Jersey", "author" : { "$oid" : "55072c56eb1a8b41906ae35c" }, "category" : "Geographical", "ratings" : [], "difficulty" : 2, "__v" : 0 }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "55072c57eb1a8b41906ae363" }, "question" : "Which state has the most national parks?", "answer" : "California", "author" : { "$oid" : "55072c56eb1a8b41906ae35c" }, "category" : "Geographical", "ratings" : [], "difficulty" : 2, "__v" : 0 }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "55072c57eb1a8b41906ae364" }, "question" : "Which state is the title of a Bruce Springsteen album?", "answer" : "Nebraska", "author" : { "$oid" : "55072c56eb1a8b41906ae35c" }, "category" : "Geographical", "ratings" : [], "difficulty" : 1, "__v" : 0 }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "55072c57eb1a8b41906ae365" }, "question" : "This state is home to Badlands National Park", "answer" : "North Dakota", "author" : { "$oid" : "55072c56eb1a8b41906ae35c" }, "category" : "Geographical", "ratings" : [], "difficulty" : 1, "__v" : 0 }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "55072e8e2942829c90aaec0a" }, "question" : "What state is known as the Lone Star State?", "answer" : "Texas", "ratings" : [], "difficulty" : 1, "__v" : 0 }
